[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Chiara.
What are you doing?
And where are you going?
Didn't I already tell you?
I don't want this anymore!
Then why are you forcing this on me?
Isn't there a better way?
You can't escape what's already been destined for you, my child.
We have reason to believe
that all this time, the Concordat has never stopped keeping an eye on you.
Then we need to do everything we can to get her back.
-It's not that easy? -You don't understand.
You owe me.
For all the sacrifices I've made. Now I'm coming to collect.
The person who I love needs my help.
-Whose could this be? -Someone from outside!
Come on, let's find out.
Ma'am. Sorry to bother you.
We found a motorcycle outside.
Looks like we may have an unauthorized visitor.
Mom. I'm going to look for Dad.
You just need to keep yourself safe.
Mom, please just listen to me.
I'll explain everything, okay?
Captain Pepe, please go to my mom.
-Please take care of her. -Okay, Mikoy.
-We'll take care of it. -Thank you.
Okay, we'll leave you now.
Mikoy, is your dad Mario missing?
You know him.
Maybe he's just being proactive.
He's looking for Chiara on his own.
So your dad does have a highly effective habit after all.
I have a hunch.
-You do? -What hunch?
I think Mario knows something.
He may have seen something or followed someone.
Mario?
Rahmboy?
-Rahmboy. -That's right.
-Mario. -But why…?
I'm just following orders.
Rahmboy.
Why didn't he tell me?
That's what I'm worried about too.
But he's trying to protect you, Mikoy.
He's trying to be a good father to you.
So what do we do now?
Call Dara and check Mario's phone.
Let's see if my hunch is right.
Sean has been talking to someone suspicious.
There's a new character in Chiara and Mikoy's lives.
And now she's a runaway bride?
We need to investigate this Vicky.
Vicky?
What does this mean?
Rahmboy?
What is this?
Have you lost your touch, Isidro?
Don't you realize the predicament you are in?
You're the one who took Chiara.
Technically, I didn't take her.
She came with me willingly.
What do you have on her that makes her obey you?
Chiara came with me because she wanted to.
She doesn't want to marry Mikoy anymore, your son.
Is that so hard to understand?
Maybe Mikoy did something to her.
Or maybe Chiara finally realized
that she doesn't really want the life in Albay.
You clearly don't understand the concept of love.
The love between those two isn't that shallow.
I don't think so either.
There's someone more suitable for Chiara,
and it's not Mikoy.
And who gave you the right to choose for Chiara?
She has parents.
Viktor and Donabel.
Being a mother isn't about blood.
I'm the one who raised her. I'm the one who sacrificed.
So I have every right.
Besides,
you're the reason
why I lost my family.
Spare me the lecture,
Mr. Butuan Executioner.
You've been enjoying your role a little too much
as a family man.
You've forgotten what you did when you were still an executioner.
My family lived a quiet life.
A simple life.
Simple dreams.
Simple joys.
But because we were poor,
we were mercilessly victimized by those in power.
That's why I swore to myself
that I would make anyone who oppressed us pay.
And your group was one of them.
Isidro Catacutan.
The man who ruined my life.
Revenge isn't easy.
Seeking justice isn't easy either.
You need power to make everyone feel
how painful it is to have a mother's heart shattered.
I promise you,
I'll make whoever did this to you pay.
That was an operation created to liberate the people
of Sitio Bungkal.
An authorized operation, yet my family got caught in it.
Was killing them authorized too?
They were innocent.
The very people who are supposed to protect the innocent
are often the ones who kill them.
Is that what you swore to do?
I fought the case.
I went everywhere.
Isidro Catacutan.
The Butuan Executioner.
But then I found out that you were supposedly dead.
I thought that weeds don't die so easily.
But what could I do?
You were supposedly dead.
So instead of seeking justice,
I went abroad.
Little did I know you were just here.
Alive and well.
With a family. Happy.
While I had to settle for loving people who weren't even related to me.
Vicky.
I know that no matter what I say,
it won't lessen the pain you're feeling right now.
I'm a parent too.
One wrong
doesn't make another wrong right.
You have no right to tell me what's right and wrong.
You killed my family.
So you should die too.
Dara said that they already found Sir Mario's location,
and they will send coordinates.
Hello? Mikoy. Sorry, it took a while,
but they were able to trace Sir Mario's location.
I'm going to do what's right.
What are you doing here?
Do you hold a grudge against me?
No, Uncle Mario.
I just owe her a debt of gratitude, that's why I follow her.
But I can't bear to see you die.
You and Aunt Tess have been good to me,
so I'm here to help you.
Thank you.
Mario.
The car keys.
Go through the back. I'm sure no one's guarding it.
Thank you.
Aren't you coming with me?
I still have something to do here.
I need to take Chiara with me.
That's what I won't allow.
Mario, leave now before I change my mind.
Chiara!
-Chiara! -What happened?
Rio has already sent someone to kill you.
You have to obey him now!
There isn't much. There are only a few of them.
Kill Rio.
So you and Mikoy can finally be free.
I'll take care of him.
Who sent you?!
Dad Mario.
Dad Mario!
Dad…
-Dad Mario. -Chiara.
This shouldn't have happened to Dad Mario.
I'll get help.
-Listen to me. -No.
No.
Hang on, Dad Mario!
I'll fix this. I'll get help.
My prayers have been answered.
Heaven is on my side.
You've lost.
Looks like we're getting close to Dad Mario.
But the tracker stopped.
So that means Chiara is here too,
if he managed to find her.
And if his tracker suddenly stopped,
then this place must have a signal jammer.
I've already contacted the local authorities.
I'll just give them the specific coordinates.
No.
You lost.
You haven't won at love yet.
Dad Mario, I'm here.
Dad Mario.
No, I'm right here, Dad Mario.
Daddy Mario!
I didn't mean to. I didn't mean to.
I didn't know.
We need you here.
You need to come here.
Let's go.
Dad.
Dad, why?
Dad!
Dad…
Dad.
Dad!
Dad…
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry.
This is my promise to you, Dad.
I will make those people pay.
The Concordat keeps getting away from us.
Does this agency even serve a purpose anymore?
You might forgot, they killed Mario Pinagpala,
the father of Mikoy!
I have to accept the fact that I'm a Valtrovi.
I will die as a true Mafia.
I will send him to where his father is now.
Don't we have connections in Prague?
Well, yes, but…
with the chance of them helping us with Chiara's case,
I doubt it very much.
It doesn't matter if you can do something about it or not.
I made a promise that I will make those people pay.
And, that's exactly what I'm going to do.